<TestItem CLASS="lecture" METHOD="list">
<skillDimension>0</skillDimension>
<itemGroup>VB496835</itemGroup>
  <LecturePicture>Poff02_jpg.jpg</LecturePicture>
  <LecturePicture>Poff02_jpg.jpg</LecturePicture>
  <LecturePicture>GetReady_gif.gif</LecturePicture>
  <LectureSound>VB496835_a01.wav</LectureSound>
  <LectureSound>VB496835_a02.wav</LectureSound>


<audio_text>Listen to part of a conversation between a student and a professor.
Hi, Professor Johnson.
Hi, Anna. What can I do for you?
 Remember, I e-mailed you about getting the handouts from the class I missed the other day, and you said I could stop by and pick them up today.
Oh, that's right.   //You know, that's the fourth class you've missed this semester, and that's not doing your grade any good.// //I assume you had a good reason for being out...//
I know, I really hated to miss another class, but I had the flu, and I could hardly get out of bed. That'll be the last class I miss, though. I promise.
Okay...So how are you feeling now—are you all recovered?
Well, I'm still not quite a hundred per cent,  but I'm feeling much better than I did a few days ago.
Well, that's good.  //Okay, uh- oh yes, the handouts. There were three of them, and I'll get those for you in just a minute. They're pretty self-explanatory, but if you have any questions, just send me an e-mail.//  But...
[interrupting] Okay, thank you.
Sure. Uh, but we also watched a video, and we'll be having an essay question about it on the next exam, so,  uh-  Hmmm-Do you have a VCR at home?
Actually, I don't, but I do have access to one.
Okay-Well I can lend it you, but the only thing is, you'd have to watch it tonight and get it back to me early tomorrow, because I'm going to be showing it in the other section of that class tomorrow afternoon.
That'd be great.
But you really have to get it back to me tomorrow before my class.
No problem. I can drop it off first thing in the morning if you'd like.
 Okay...  You know what? How about if we do it this way. I'll keep it for now and show it in my class tomorrow, and uh then you can drop by here and pick it up on Friday morning and keep it for the whole weekend, and just bring it with you when you come to class next week. How does that sound?  Uh then you'll have a couple of days to watch it, and you won't have to worry about getting it back here tomorrow.
 Let's see, Friday morning...  Yeah, that'll work.
Excellent. I'll be here from about ten to eleven thirty.
 Great. I'll see you then.
Uh, just a second. Let me get you those handouts.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.</audio_text>


</TestItem>